<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
    <core_body>
        ### Apple iOS
        **How it Works**
        The message appears after 2 seconds (customizable) from page load, and is destroyed after 20 seconds (also customizable). The balloon enters and exits the screen
        with a quick configurable animation: drop from top, bubble from bottom or fade in/out.
        The balloon can be dismissed any time by tapping the small “x” icon. The script also checks the user locale and shows the message in an appropriate language.

        ✓ following languages are supported: Catalan Chinese (Traditional and Simplified) Danish Dutch English Finnish French German Greek Hebrew Hungarian Italian
        Japanese Korean Norwegian Portuguese Russian Spanish Swedish Thai Turkish

        **Custom Startup images **
        Often call also splash screen: the splash screen is a rectangular or full screen image which appears while a software product is loading (OS, CAD, game, etc).
        Often it contains a progress bar, indicating the loading phases.
        Specifying a startup image is available in iOS 3.0 and later. On iOS, similar to native applications, you can specify a startup image that is displayed while your
        website application launches. This is especially useful when your web application is offline. By default, a screenshot of the web application the last time it was
        launched is used.

        ✓ You can provide up to 7 startup images!
        ✓ If images are not of the corrected size, the image will be scale automatically up or down by CedAdd2Home. It is recommended is to provide the correct size for
        best result

        **Custom icon to springboard**
        You may want users to be able to add your web application or webpage link to the Home screen. These links, represented by an icon, are called Web Clips.

        ✓ You can provide up to 7 custom icons for all iPhone, iPad being retina, mini running iOS7/8+ or still running under iOS6!
        ✓ If images are not of the corrected size, the image will be scale automatically up or down by CedAdd2Home. It is recommended is to provide the correct size for
        best result

        **Custom Messages**
        It is possible to override the default message to invite user to add your site to their home screen.


        ### Windows 8.1 tiles
        *★ premium version only*

        With Internet Explorer, users can put their favorite Web sites right beside their favorite apps by pinning them to the Windows and Windows Phone Start Screens.
        Pinning Web sites from IE gives users immediate access to these sites from the Start Screen without having to navigate to them repeatedly.

        When users pin your site, they have indicated that they are frequent visitors of your site and care about updates from it. With that in mind, Internet Explorer
        now brings you Live Tiles for Web sites, allowing you to keep your users connected to your Web site outside of the browser.

        With Live Tiles, you can engage with your users by bringing fresh content such as breaking news, new message alerts or titles of new blog posts right to their
        Start Screen. Furthermore, you can support multiple tile sizes for your Web site, allowing users to display your site prominently as wide or large tiles.

        Windows Desktop and Windows Mobile are also supported by CedAdd2Home

        **Notifications / Live Tile to your website**
        Live Tiles for Web sites are powered by Periodic Notifications, wherein the platform pulls text and images from polling uris hosted on a server at a predefined
        polling interval, and displays this content on the Web site’s tile.

        With Windows 8.1, pinned site tiles can notify a user outside Internet Explorer 11 and pull them right back in! If you have a web feed, you can automatically
        build notifications into your tile. Who said RSS was dead? If you don't have one, skip this step. You can choose to implement custom tile notifications later.

        The polling uris defined in this example contain the contents of the notification to be displayed and will be polled every half an hour. Therefore in a given 30
        minute interval, a user can see up to 5 updates from this site, keeping your user intimately connected with your Web site at all times.

        You can use 1 to 5 URL to your RSS feed in CedAdd2Home.

        ### Windows 7
        *★ premium version only*
        Your site feels more like a native app in Internet Explorer 9 through pinning. Discover a new way to get more results from your Windows 7 users on the web,
        reaching nearly 35% in the USA and over 21% worldwide.

        Test it by dragging your site tab to the Windows 7 taskbar when CedAdd2Home premium is installed.

        **hi-res favicon support**
        Your site's logo lights-up on the Windows taskbar when it’s high-resolution. When users pin your site, they become your most loyal customers. Give them a
        one-click experience that brings them back again and again.

        **Jump List**
        Your site is more than a home page. You have great content but users don’t always get to it. Inspire them to go deeper with Jump Lists. There are two types:
        Static Jump List: Use these to promote the most common places you want your users to go
        Dynamic Jump List: Use these to get creative, pulling your users in with the latest articles, personalized deals, or trending topics

        **Notifications**
        How do you catch user attention when they’re not actively browsing your site? Pull them with a timely notification. Use an icon overlay when new content is
        available or flash the taskbar to show when user action is requested just like an app.

        ### Android
        *★ premium version only*
        The message appears after 2 seconds (customizable) from page load, and is destroyed after 20 seconds (also customizable). The balloon enters and exits the screen
        with a quick configurable animation: drop from top, bubble from bottom or fade in/out.
        The balloon can be dismissed any time by tapping the small “x” icon. The script also checks the user locale and shows the message in an appropriate language.

        ✓ following languages are supported: Catalan Chinese (Traditional and Simplified) Danish Dutch English Finnish French German Greek Hebrew Hungarian Italian
        Japanese Korean Norwegian Portuguese Russian Spanish Swedish Thai Turkish

        ### Resume

        ✓ Make Joomla appear like a standard native application
        ✓ Autostarts on page load
        ✓ Show the message to returning visitors only
        ✓ Animations for display and exit
        ✓ Message auto hide
        ✓ Custom message
        ✓ Customizable appearance

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedadd2home-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedadd2home-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedadd2home-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedadd2home-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>