<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
    <core_body>
        CedDisqusComments is a powerful content plugin that allows for easy integration of Disqus comment system.

        ### Disqus
        Disqus, Inc. is a blog comment hosting service for websites and online communities that uses a networked platform. The company’s platform includes various
        features, such as social integration, social networking, user profiles, spam and moderation tools, analytics, email notifications, and mobile commenting. It was
        founded in 2007 by Daniel Ha and Jason Yan as a Y Combinator startup.
        Disqus ranks #1 in Quantcast's U.S. networks with 144 million monthly unique U.S. visits Disqus is featured on many major publications, such as CNN, Daily
        Telegraph and IGN and about 750,000 blogs and websites.It competes with IntenseDebate, Livefyre and Echo.

        **CedDisqusComments **is the simpliest DISQUS plugin that simply works!

        ### Why using CedDisqusComments?
        The Comments box lets people comment on content on your site using their Disqus profile and shows this activity to their friends in news feed. It also contains
        built-in moderation tools and special social relevance ranking.

        ### Features
        ✓ Width of the comments box
        ✓ Should a comments counter be displayed in all views except the article view.
        ✓ Enable comment icon if count is shown. Choose among 7 Icons in frontpage to let user add comments,
        ✓ Support Font-Awesome
        ✓ Responsive design for mobile site
        ✓ Add Disqus comments to selected or all Joomla categories,

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.

        WHY CHOOSE DISQUS? HIGHLIGHTS OF THE DISQUS COMMENT SYSTEM

        Web comments can be difficult for both websites and their readers. We think Disqus is the solution. Disqus makes it easier for people to comment and track their contributions on a single profile which they can display as a comment blog. After all, there is no difference between a great comment and a great published article.

        Disqus makes managing discussions on one or multiple websites painless. With a powerful and intuitive admin interface, Disqus allows website owners to spend time elsewhere while Disqus takes care of the comments.

        Key benefits for Websites, Publishers, Bloggers
        * Threaded comments and comment ratings
        * Powerful moderation and admin tools
        * Filter out spam, trolls, and unwanted commenters
        * Enable your visitors to become a real community
        * Moderation by email or mobile
        * More comments and increased engagement
        * Connected with a large discussion community
        * Increased exposure and readership

        Key benefits for Commenters, Readers
        * Track and manage comments and replies
        * Verified commenter reputations across sites
        * More control over your own comments on websites
        * Never lose your comments, even if the website goes away
        * Build a global profile, or comment blog, to collect and show off what you're saying
        * Easier to comment on websites using Disqus
        * Reply to comments through email or mobile
        * Edit and republish comments with one click
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/ceddisquscomments-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/ceddisquscomments-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/ceddisquscomments-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/ceddisquscomments-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>