<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://www.galaxiis.com/jed/jedupdate.xsd"
           xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <core_body>
        CedFacebookComments is a powerful content plugin that allows for easy integration of Facebook comment system.

        ### Disqus
        Disqus, Inc. is a blog comment hosting service for websites and online communities that uses a networked platform. The company’s platform includes various
        features, such as social integration, social networking, user profiles, spam and moderation tools, analytics, email notifications, and mobile commenting. It was
        founded in 2007 by Daniel Ha and Jason Yan as a Y Combinator startup.
        Disqus ranks #1 in Quantcast's U.S. networks with 144 million monthly unique U.S. visits Disqus is featured on many major publications, such as CNN, Daily
        Telegraph and IGN and about 750,000 blogs and websites.It competes with IntenseDebate, Livefyre and Echo.

        ✓ Width of the comments box
        ✓ Order comments by Times (oldest at top) or Social or Reverse
        ✓ Comments Moderators
        ✓ Themes light or dark
        ✓ Should a comments counter be displayed in all views except the article view.
        ✓ Enable comment icon if count is shown. Choose among 7 Icons in frontpage to let user add comments,
        ✓ Support Font-Awesome
        ✓ Responsive design for mobile site
        ✓ Add Facebook comments to selected or all Joomla categories,

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        We receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>

    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfacebookcomments-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfacebookcomments-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfacebookcomments-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfacebookcomments-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>