<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
    <core_body>
        Embedding FreeMind mind map into Joomla has never been so easy! CedFreemind use a Flash browser to display your FreeMind map.

        ### Features
        ✓ Display unlimited number of Freemind maps into articles
        ✓ Zooming, Auto Fit to screen
        ✓ Search through node
        ✓ Node states can be configured (collapsed, unfold all)
        ✓ Customization of appearance

        *★ premium version only*
        ✓ Display mindmap in module
        ✓ Support


        ### Why using CedFreemind?
        FreeMind is a free mind mapping application written in Java. FreeMind is licensed under the GNU General Public License. It provides extensive export capabilities.
        It runs on Microsoft Windows, Linux and Mac OS X via the Java Runtime Environment.

        As with other mind mapping software packages, FreeMind allows the user to edit a hierarchical set of ideas around a central concept. The non-linear approach
        assists in brainstorming new outlines and projects as ideas are added around the mind map.

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfreemind-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfreemind-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfreemind-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedfreemind-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>
