<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://www.galaxiis.com/jed/jedupdate.xsd"
           xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <core_body>
        CedGallerySlider is touch swipe (touch+drag+move) and Responsive image slider with 360+ java script slideshow effects. With more than 30+ themes, it's easy to
        work out image slider, content slider, fade slideshow, thumbnail slider, nested slider, carousel slider, slider cluster, full width slider, grid slider, list
        slider, vertical slider, image gallery, banner slider, banner rotator, video gallery for website, web page presentation.

        CedGallerySlider is the most feature complete slider and will help you creating attractive image sliders and displaying photos as a slideshow with fancy
        transition effects on your website!

        ### Features
        ✓ 100% based on HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.
        ✓ Display all images stored in a directory
        ✓ As navigation you can use thumbnails, arrows or bullets,
        ✓ Read IPTC and EXIF data to create title and descriptions,
        ✓ Automatic thumbnails creation
        ✓ Sorting by Date using Exif data,
        ✓ SEO (Search Engine Optimization) friendly
        ✓ Animated captions, responsive layout and touch support for mobile devices
        ✓ High performance and cross-browser compatibility,
        ✓ Super-easy installation and management,
        ✓ Flexible settings and robust stability
        ✓ Thumbnail size, style

        ### Touch swipe and responsive
        Touch swipe and responsive image slider for mobile, tablet and desktop. All devices supported: Android, iOS and Windows Phone.

        ### All browser supported
        CedGallerySlider is tested regularly with all major browsers. Chrome 3+, Firefox 2+, IE 6+, Safari 3.1+ and Opera 10+

        ### 390+ Transitions
        More than 390+ caption slide effects and fancy transition effects to choose from! Choose one or many amazing visual effects.

        ### 30+ Templates
        Easy to use administrator panel to create fantastic sliders in a matter of seconds without coding and image editing.

        ### Rocking Fast
        CedGallerySlider uses techniques like lazy load for optimal performance. All code has been carefully optimized for speed.

        ### All in one!
        CedGallerySlider is an image slider, content slider, fade slideshow, thumbnail slider, nested slider, carousel slider, slider cluster, full width slider, grid
        slider, list slider, vertical slider, image gallery, banner slider, banner rotator, video gallery, tiled menu slider all in one!

        ### One Click Install
        CedGallerySlider is using Joomla packaging and installs with 1 click one components and 1 modules.

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgalleryslider-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgalleryslider-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgalleryslider-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgalleryslider-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>
