<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://www.galaxiis.com/jed/jedupdate.xsd"
           xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <core_body>
        CedGoogleAjaxCDN use content distribution network (CDN) for loading the most popular open-source JavaScript libraries. The Google Hosted Libraries provides your
        applications with stable, reliable, high-speed, globally available access to all of the most popular, open-source JavaScript libraries. By using this network your
        site will gain speed as user will load library only once for all and from the fastest and closest local server!

        ### You get more speed because
        * Decreased latency: jquery, bootstrap wont be loaded from your site but from google servers
        * Increased parallelism: Using the Google AJAX Libraries CDN eliminates one request to your site, allowing more of your local content to downloaded in parallel!
        * Better caching: when a browser sees references to CDN-hosted copies of libraries, it understands that all of those references do refer to the exact same file
        and wont load them multiple times

        ### Features
        ✓ Use Google Hosted Libraries
        ✓ Replace major version of Javascript librariries
        ✓ Bootstrap
        ✓ Mootols
        ✓ Jquery
        ✓ Both for frontend and backend

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgoogleajaxcdn-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgoogleajaxcdn-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgoogleajaxcdn-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgoogleajaxcdn-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>