<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
    <core_body>
        CedGooglePlusComments is a powerful content plugin that allows for easy integration of Google+ comment system.

        ### Google+
        Google+ Comments look similar to traditional Facebook comments, but have some important differences. For example:
        When you leave a comment on a blog, you'll see the option, checked by default, to also share that comment to Google+..
        Google+ posts that link to blog posts will show up as a comment underneath those blog posts.
        If original comment is shared to Google+, replies to the comment on the blog will show up in Google+ and vice versa, but only to the people that the original
        comment was shared with.
        If a comment is not shared with the blog author, the blog author will not be able to see the comment in either location.
        As the author of a post, you’ll receive Google+ notifications when readers comment on or share your blog post.
        What if my readers don’t have a Google+ profile or page? Can they still comment? No, but they will be prompted to create one when they attempt to comment.

        Google+ Comments is not available for private blogs and for blogs with adult content.

        What happens when I remove a comment? Removing a Google+ comment will only affect the comment in the particular location you removed it from. For example, someone
        might create a public Google+ post that links to your blog post -- and since it links to your blog post, it'll show up as a comment on your blog. You can remove
        the instance of this post from your blog, but your removal won't affect the original post from showing up on Google+.

        ### Features
        ✓ Width of the comments box
        ✓ Display social interactions made on Google Plus.
        ✓ Themes light or dark
        ✓ Comments moderation support. (If you provide a Google+ Profile ID)
        ✓ Should a comments counter be displayed in all views except the article view.
        ✓ Enable comment icon if count is shown. Choose among 7 Icons in frontpage to let user add comments,
        ✓ Support Font-Awesome
        ✓ Responsive design: works on Mobiles and desktop
        ✓ HTML5 implementation
        ✓ Add Google+ comments to selected or all Joomla categories,

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgooglepluscomments-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgooglepluscomments-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgooglepluscomments-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedgooglepluscomments-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>
