<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
<core_body>
SmugMug makes it easy to safely store, share and sell your photos online. Gorgeous, secure, online photo sharing. CedSmugmug add support for SmugMug in Joomla.

This package all you ever need to support Smugmug library in Joomla.

### Features
✓ Embed Slideshow into articles or modules,
✓ Embed Flash badge into articles or modules,
✓ Embed Video player into articles or modules,
✓ Use RSS SmugMug API,

### 4 Joomla modules
* Smugmug badge: display an elegant badge using Adobe Flash and use up to 1 gallery.
* Smugmug random: display random pictures from up to 4 galleries.
* Smugmug slideshow: display an elegant slideshow using Adobe Flash and use up to 1 gallery
* Smugmug video: display HD/SD quality videos.

### 4 Joomla content plugins
* Smugmug random: display random pictures into any Joomla article.
* Smugmug slideshow: display an elegant slideshow using Adobe Flash into any Joomla article.
* Smugmug video: display video using Adobe Flash into any Joomla article.
* Smugmug badge: display html5 badge into any Joomla article.

### 3 Joomla editor plugin
* Smugmug random editor button: to allow easy addition of random pictures into any Joomla article.
* Smugmug slideshow editor button: to allow easy addition of slideshow using Adobe Flash into any Joomla article.
* Smugmug video editor button: to allow easy addition of video into any Joomla article.

### 2 type of Slideshows output: Javascript or Adobe Flash.

* Javascript
- Responsive design
- No Flash required
- Lightweight (4-12Kb)
- Prev/Next controls
- Customizable speed, delay, size etc.
- Cross-browser compatibility
- Search engine friendly
- Clean and valid markup

* Adobe Flash
- Responsive design
- Official Flash slideshow
- Prev/Next controls
- Customizable speed, delay, size etc.
- Cross-browser compatibility
- Major Browsers Support.
- HTML5, CSS3, UTF-8

### Why using SmugMug?
SmugMug is a paid digital photo sharing website, founded by Chris and Don MacAskill in 2002.
SmugMug is a paid photo-sharing website and image hosting service which allows users to upload both HD photos and videos to their SmugMug sites. Launched in 2002 the company offers a tool set which facilitates the selling of digital and print media for amateur and professional photographers. Pro photographers, passionate amateurs and photo lovers get big, beautiful and customizable online galleries for easy sharing, printing and archiving.
* Unlimited uploads of photos and videos.
* Big, gorgeous galleries with no shrinkage whatsoever.
* Easy drag and drop uploads from your desktop or direct from your photo apps.
* One-click sharing to Facebook, Twitter, blogs and email.
* Built-in marketing tools for pros.
* Customizable gallery and photo privacy options.
* Easy order fulfillment through two print labs.
* Full control over your site's look and feel.
* No ads or spam, period.

### You're part of our marketing team!
At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

### Satisfaction Guarantee
If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we will refund your money.
</core_body>

<homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsmugmug-showcase/</homepage_link>
<download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsmugmug-download/</download_link>
<demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsmugmug-demo/</demo_link>
<documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsmugmug-doc/</documentation_link>
<support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
<license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
<version>%%version%%</version>
<compatibility>
<version>25</version>
<version>30</version>
</compatibility>
</jedupdate>
