<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
<core_body>
This plugin add automatically to any article a set of social icons that let your reader increase your social ranking.
It support
★ Twitter
★ Facebook
★ Digg
★ Linkedin social network Share button.
★ Xing
★ StumbleUpon 
★ Pinterest

Choose which buttons to show and where to show them in your Joomla com_content. Include or exclude specific articles, sections or categories. Your visitors still stay on your site, so you do not loose visitors to other sites. 

### Features
★ All button display a counter based on your settings
★ Run with NO 3rd party providers like ShareThis for example, only         use official providers (Google, facebook and so on)
★ Ability to turn on and turn off the desired networks.
★ Ability to define the visibility in the desired category articles.
★ Ability to define on top or bottom of the article.
★ Ability to show on frontpage.

Multiple position are possible within your articles
★ left, right: in the margin of your articles
★ left-full, right-full: take whole line
★ floating

### You're part of our marketing team!
We receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

### Satisfaction Guarantee
If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we will refund your money.
</core_body>

<homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsocialsharinglive-showcase/</homepage_link>
<download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsocialsharinglive-download/</download_link>
<demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsocialsharinglive-demo/</demo_link>
<documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsocialsharinglive-doc/</documentation_link>
<support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
<license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>

    <version>%%version%%</version>

<compatibility>
    <version>25</version>
    <version>30</version>
    <version>31</version>
    <version>32</version>
    <version>33</version>
</compatibility>
</jedupdate>
