<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">

    <core_body>
        Ever been to a site where you had to register and the registration form required that you type in the same phrase that is found in a hard-to-read image? Joomla!
        has now this possibility thanks to my extension CedSecurityimages. It will protect You against most spammers attempt!

        ### Features
        * Support best online captcha services: Recapctha, KeyCaptcha and NuCaptcha
        * Protect all JForm Field of all Joomla! extensions without ANY patches to Joomla! core or extensions
        * Good and configurable captcha

        ### Why using CedSecurityImages?
        CedSecurityImages protect all Form in joomla without any hacks or Joomla core changes.
        CedSecurityImages produce CAPTCHA (an acronym for "Completely Automated Public Turing test to tell Computers and Humans Apart") is a type of challenge-response
        test used in computing to determine whether or not the user is human.

        CAPTCHAs are used to prevent bots from using various types of computing services or collecting certain types of sensitive information. Applications include
        preventing bots from taking part in online polls, registering for free email accounts (which may then be used to send spam) and collecting email addresses.

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        At Galaxiis.com we receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsecurityimages-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsecurityimages-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsecurityimages-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedsecurityimages-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>