<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jedupdate version="1">
    <core_body>
        CedTwitterCards gives users greater context and insight into the URLs shared on Twitter, which in turn allows Twitter to send more engaged traffic to your site or
        app. Twitter cards make it possible for you to attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpages, and
        users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their followers..
        Improve representation of your content within Tweets across the web and on mobile devices.

        In addition to displaying your content in a more engaging way, CedTwitterCards can also drive downloads of your mobile applications. you'll be able to specify
        downloads for users who've not yet installed your app on their device.

        This will work across iPhone, iPad, and Android (Google Play). Please note that if you have an iPhone app, but no iPad-optimized app, you should include the
        iPhone app id, name, and url for both iPhone and iPad-related tags.
        When no value is provided, the Cards will simply render a "View on web" link pointing title, description, thumbnail are automatically taken from the current
        article without any user intervention

        The Summary Card can be used for many kinds of web content, from blog posts and news articles, to products and restaurants.

        What happens when I remove a comment? Removing a Google+ comment will only affect the comment in the particular location you removed it from. For example, someone
        might create a public Google+ post that links to your blog post -- and since it links to your blog post, it'll show up as a comment on your blog. You can remove
        the instance of this post from your blog, but your removal won't affect the original post from showing up on Google+.

        ### Features
        ✓ Display your content in a more engaging way
        ✓ Add Summary Card (Default card), that include a title, description, thumbnail, and Twitter account attribution
        ✓ Get the description text from introduction text and or full text
        ✓ Support Joomla publisher and authors
        ✓ Attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content.
        ✓ Users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their followers.
        ✓ Automatic thumbnails detection and generation
        ✓ Description origin configurable
        ✓ Thumbnails origin configurable
        ✓ Add iOS Application download link
        ✓ Add Android Application download link
        ✓ Deep-link into your own iOS/Android app

        ### You're part of our marketing team!
        We receive feedback from our customers and consistently turn their comments and suggestions into new and improved features.

        ### Satisfaction Guarantee
        If you are not totally satisfied with our product or installation, we will promptly resolve any issues. In the event you are still not completely satisfied, we
        will refund your money.
    </core_body>
    <homepage_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedtwittercard-showcase/</homepage_link>
    <download_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedtwittercard-download/</download_link>
    <demo_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedtwittercard-demo/</demo_link>
    <documentation_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/cedtwittercard-doc/</documentation_link>
    <support_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/forums/</support_link>
    <license_link>https://www.galaxiis.com/licence/</license_link>
    <version>%%version%%</version>
    <compatibility>
        <version>30</version>
    </compatibility>
</jedupdate>
